PRASAD WAGHMARE

HR & FINANACE

Professional Summary

I've worked hard in career and now I want to grow my knowledge with practice. While working with my previous organizations I had a lot of exposure to the business environment. A lot of my courses involved working with real companies to solve real problems and issues. From Previous experiences I have learned lot of things and like Audit preparations, HR management, Accounts handling, Recruitment, Reports and inductions, Leadership and operation handling, vendor management. Client Handling, Payroll Management, Trainings, Performance management, Compliances management, Presentation skills, Audit skills, Other skills.



Contact

Address

VISHWAVIDYA SOCIETY, WARJE, PUNE, INDIA 411058

Phone

8379810944 / 9011727951

E-mail

PW15091999@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/pr asa d-waghmare-007

Skills

GOOD COMMUNICATION
Advanced

QUICK LERNER Advanced

Work History

Jan 2023 - Current

HR Generalist - P24 SERVICES PROPERTY SOLUTIONS PVT LTD, PUNE

- Reviewed existing policies and procedures to make recommendations for enhancing work productivity, recruitment, hiring processes, and compliances.
- Performance management, Induction, joining and onboarding.
- Planned for Audits and documentations.
- Handle the attendance, Payroll, PF, ESIC, Other compliances.
- Warning and termination letters, Absconding letters.
- Work on Salary breakup and offer letters and appointment letter.
- Sites audit and reports.
- RNR, Site training and Audits.
- Salary negotiation and breakup preparation.
- Resolve the compliances and grievances issues of site staff.
- Employee engagement and other activity.
- Attendance and Performance management.
- Introduce creative ideas and new policies.
- ISO Audit and certification.
- Client coordination

Mar, 2022 - Dec, 2022

HR Executive - Bloofield Management Services LLP. (Facility Management), Pune

 Researched and analyzed human resources trends and best practices and drove corporate policy changes to optimize business performance. DEDICATED AND CREATIVE Advanced

Languages

English

Upper intermediate

Marathi

Upper intermediate

Hindi

Upper intermediate

Education

2023-01 - 2024-12

MBA: HR And Finance

MBA - Welingkar Institute of Management (Mumbai)

2017-06 - 2022-10

B. Com: (Costing)

SMACC - PUNE

2015-06 - 2017-06

HSC:

NAVBHARAT

HIGHSCHOOL - Pune

- Within this position I was responsible for recruit and hire employees for head office.
- Site Visits for training and Audits
- Salary discussion and onboarding
- Joining and induction process
- Documentation and salary negotiations
- Monthly training reports preparation and share to client
- Warning, Termination, Absconding, offer letters preparation and other verifications and client coordination.

Jul, 2021 – Feb, 2022 (Company relocated to Bangalore)

Accounts & HR Executive - PRAYASTA 3D INVENTIONS PVT

LTD (STARTUP), PUNE

- Due to startup used to handle multiple work and responsibilities.
- Book-keeping and accounting
- Used to maintain book of Accounts through software Zoho-books
- GST & TDS working
- GST and TDS Filing
- find new vendors for the requirements
- reconciliation of transactions
- Built and strengthened relationships with new and existing accounts to drive revenue growth.
- Audit and other HR activities

Aug, 2020 – Jul, 2021 (Contractual for 11 months)

LDC (Audit Section) - Garrison Engineering R&D (DEFENCE), PUNE

- It was a first job which was on contractual basis for a year.
- · Here i used to handle email coordination's.
- Cross check all the data and Audit for multiple sites
- Verify all the documentation and forward to accounts manager.
- Accounting and verifying the audits.
- Worked effectively in fast-paced environments.
- Good communication skills, both verbal and written.
- Passionate about learning and committed to continual improvement.

Thank you for your time. I look forward to speaking with you about my experience and passion for all aspects.

THANK YOU FOR CONSIDERING!